The hard part for many product people is not prompting.
It is getting past installs, Git, folders, builds, and authentication.
PPP starts where familiar browser tools start:
open a project and describe the outcome.
The first result is a real browser game.
Its timer and keyboard behavior are already running, with no refresh.
Now the same conversation crosses the server boundary
and adds product accounts without replacing the game.
Product work is iterative. The first form is not good enough,
so I ask for a better interface and useful errors.
This error comes from the real account boundary. I fix the input,
create a player, sign out, sign back in, and the session survives reload.
Next, Snake becomes a service. The signed-in player saves a score
through a server action into SQLite.
The ranking is server-owned data, not a painted mockup.
The account and score remain after reload.
A product decision changes the shape of the whole service.
Snake is now one game in a platform, without losing its users or data.
One more conversation adds a second game
while preserving everything that already works.
Tetris runs in the browser. Accounts and rankings stay on the server.
Both evolve inside one live product workspace.
Where product conversations become running software.